<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Feature SiLA2Version="1.0" FeatureVersion="1.0" Originator="de.cetoni" Category="core" xmlns="http://www.sila-standard.org" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.sila-standard.org https://gitlab.com/SiLA2/sila_base/raw/master/schema/FeatureDefinition.xsd">
    <Identifier>ShutdownController</Identifier>
    <DisplayName>Shutdown Controller</DisplayName>
    <Description>
        Provides a generic way of telling a SiLA2 server that it is about to be shut down or to shut down itself. The server implements a routine to be executed before the hardware is shut down (e.g. saving device parameters or bringing the device into a safe position) and may also be capable of shutting itself down completely.
    </Description>

    <!-- Commands -->
    <Command>
        <Identifier>PrepareShutdown</Identifier>
        <DisplayName>Prepare Shutdown</DisplayName>
        <Description>
            Initiates the pre-shutdown routine. If no errors occurred during this process the server should be considered ready to be physically shutdown (i.e. the device can be shut down/powered off). Shutting down the server must be done manually, e.g. by unplugging the power to the device.
        </Description>
        <Observable>Yes</Observable>
        <DefinedExecutionErrors>
            <Identifier>PrepareShutdownFailed</Identifier>
        </DefinedExecutionErrors>
    </Command>
    <Command>
        <Identifier>Shutdown</Identifier>
        <DisplayName>Shutdown</DisplayName>
        <Description>
            Initiates the shutdown routine. This first executes the pre-shutdown routine (to store parameters, bring the device in a safe position, etc.) and then physically shuts down the device. If errors occurred during the pre-shutdown process the server is considered not ready to be physically shutdown (i.e. the device will not be shut down/powered off).
        </Description>
        <Observable>Yes</Observable>
        <DefinedExecutionErrors>
            <Identifier>PrepareShutdownFailed</Identifier>
        </DefinedExecutionErrors>
    </Command>

    <!-- Errors -->
    <DefinedExecutionError>
        <Identifier>PrepareShutdownFailed</Identifier>
        <DisplayName>Prepare Shutdown Failed</DisplayName>
        <Description>
            The pre-shutdown routine was not executed properly. The server is not ready to be physically shutdown.
        </Description>
    </DefinedExecutionError>
</Feature>
